//-----------------------SET 1-------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nhew",
//     "answer": "when"
//   }, // Answer: police
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lifaym ",
//     "answer": "family"
//   }, // Answer: alert
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "atbel",
//     "answer": "table"
//   }, // Answer: blink
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eomhwrok",
//     "answer": "homework "
//   }, // Answer: worth
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "rettrac",
//     "answer": "tractor"
//   }, // Answer: lover
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "siatn",
//     "answer": "stain"
//   }, // Answer: brilliant
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "sebirt",
//     "answer": "tribes"
//   }, // Answer: tribes
//   // Answer:  particles
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "roetmh",
//     "answer": "mother"
//   },
//   // Answer: chains
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "teag",
//     "answer": "gate"
//   }, // Answer: mails
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "Voide",
//     "answer": "video"
//   }, // Answer:  particles
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "resist",
//     "answer": "sister "
//   }, // Answer: chains
// ];

//------------------------SET 2--------------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "thapnele",
//     "answer": "elephant"
//   }, // Answer: police
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ricfonit",
//     "answer": "friction"
//   }, // Answer: alert
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "akhopra",
//     "answer": "pokhara "
//   }, // Answer: blink
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ngdar",
//     "answer": "grand"
//   }, // Answer: worth
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nnaaurpna",
//     "answer": "annapurna"
//   }, // Answer: lover
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "otemupcr",
//     "answer": "computer"
//   }, // Answer: brilliant
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "sserurep",
//     "answer": "pressure"
//   }, // Answer: react
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nievruse",
//     "answer": "universe"
//   }
// ];

//----------------SET 3 --------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "oykrdbae",
//     "answer": "keyboard"
//   }, // Answer: police
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "tnolrecnie",
//     "answer": "electronic"
//   }, // Answer: alert
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "antuomni",
//     "answer": "mountain"
//   }, // Answer: blink
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "onmrfi",
//     "answer": "inform"
//   }, // Answer: worth
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nacs",
//     "answer": "scan"
//   }, // Answer: lover
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "arsdatuy",
//     "answer": "saturday"
//   }, // Answer: brilliant
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "etymapn",
//     "answer": "payment"
//   }, // Answer: react
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "noli",
//     "answer": "lion "
//   }, // Answer: mails
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "erhew",
//     "answer": "where "
//   }, // Answer:  particles
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ogman",
//     "answer": "mango"
//   }, // Answer: chains
// ];

//-------------------SET 4 -----------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "suemo",
//     "answer": "mouse"
//   }, // Answer: police
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "evusn",
//     "answer": "venus"
//   }, // Answer: alert
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eson",
//     "answer": "nose"
//   }, // Answer: blink
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "celpin",
//     "answer": "pencil"
//   }, // Answer: worth
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "anroge",
//     "answer": "orange"
//   }, // Answer: lover
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eppar",
//     "answer": "paper"
//   }, // Answer: brilliant
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "kdsu",
//     "answer": "dusk"
//   }, // Answer: react
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eoshr",
//     "answer": "horse "
//   }, // Answer: mails
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "kicehcn",
//     "answer": "chicken "
//   }, // Answer:  particles
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lidnbgui",
//     "answer": "building"
//   }, // Answer: chains
// ];

// ---------------------SET 5-------------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "qutsere",
//     "answer": "request"
//   }, // Answer: Request
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lims",
//     "answer": "slim"
//   }, // Answer: slim
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ydomna",
//     "answer": "monday"
//   }, // Answer:  saturday
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "evsun",
//     "answer": "venus"
//   }, // Answer: venus
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "erared",
//     "answer": "reader"
//   }, // Answer: lime
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "anroge",
//     "answer": "orange"
//   }, // Answer: orange
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "neficfistu",
//     "answer": "sufficient"
//   }, // Answer: sufficient
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ecdorr",
//     "answer": "record"
//   }, // Answer: record
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "trgae",
//     "answer": "great"
//   }, // Answer: nose
// ];

// ------------SET 6---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "unmot",
//     "answer": "mount"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "yaprt",
//     "answer": "party "
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "phgar",
//     "answer": "graph"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "oivde",
//     "answer": "video"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "rendst",
//     "answer": "trends"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "thacr",
//     "answer": "chart"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nodur",
//     "answer": "round"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nedcso",
//     "answer": "second"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "aknbl",
//     "answer": "blank"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ioadr",
//     "answer": "radio"
//   }
// ];

// ------------SET 7---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ntealphe",
//     "answer": "elephant"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eotcmupr",
//     "answer": "computer"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "asktballbe",
//     "answer": "basketball"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "gnaulgea",
//     "answer": "language"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "dvnretaeu",
//     "answer": "adventure"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "yftubtrei",
//     "answer": "butterfly"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "piraenla",
//     "answer": "airplane"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "phinaessh",
//     "answer": "happiness"
//   }
// ];

// ------------SET 8---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "bitarb",
//     "answer": "rabbit"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "kcteor",
//     "answer": "rocket"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "scaaub",
//     "answer": "abacus"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eumcrtpo",
//     "answer": "computer"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "engydrho",
//     "answer": "hydrogen"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "gsrnto",
//     "answer": "strong"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ommrosascl",
//     "answer": "classroom"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "rtesnep",
//     "answer": "present"
//   }
// ];

// ------------SET 10---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "tordoc",
//     "answer": "doctor"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lwpalepr",
//     "answer": "wallpaper"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "enkowdelg",
//     "answer": "knowledge"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eblife",
//     "answer": "belief"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ehilevc",
//     "answer": "vehicle"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "dsuotie",
//     "answer": "outside"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "egren",
//     "answer": "green"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "iiemdcne",
//     "answer": "medicine"
//   }
// ];

// ------------SET 12---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "ooshlc", "answer": "school"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "ymecorne", "answer": "ceremony"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "ipncic", "answer": "picnic"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "sroty", "answer": "story"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "uqltayi", "answer": "quality"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "tofromc", "answer": "comfort"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "tigrh", "answer": "right"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "lpate", "answer": "plate"}
// ];

// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "alpcae", "answer": "place"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "efkin", "answer": "knife"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "plpeeo", "answer": "people"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "lmiyfa", "answer": "family"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "ttiyhr", "answer": "thirty"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "etnoda", "answer": "donate"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "uerutf", "answer": "future"},
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": "hvnaee", "answer": "heaven"}
// ];

// ------------SET Semi Final 1---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "uftbaueil",
//     "answer": "beautiful"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lnurtaa",
//     "answer": "natural"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "ucsero",
//     "answer": "source"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "tsreis",
//     "answer": "sister"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "rwylea",
//     "answer": "lawyer"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eunsdtt",
//     "answer": "student"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "rtberoh",
//     "answer": "brother"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "papel",
//     "answer": "apple"
//   }
// ];

// ------------SET Semi Final-2---------------------//
// final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
//   {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "nhucl",
//     "answer": "lunch"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "yenho",
//     "answer": "honey"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lwfroe",
//     "answer": "flower"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "troesf",
//     "answer": "forest"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "lainma",
//     "answer": "animal"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "eicmrcae",
//     "answer": "icecream"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "termwaonel",
//     "answer": "watermelon"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
//     "word": "rarcto",
//     "answer": "carrot"
//   }
// ];

// ------------SET Final---------------------//
final List<Map<String, String>> QuestionList = [
  {"question": "Unscramble the following word:", "word": ""},
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "gudrno",
    "answer": "ground"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "ecetahr",
    "answer": "teacher"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "alhetht",
    "answer": "health"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "notfcuin",
    "answer": "function"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "rbina",
    "answer": "brain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "rfvee",
    "answer": "fever"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "nonutima",
    "answer": "mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unscramble the following word:",
    "word": "eawtr",
    "answer": "water"
  }
];
